Guide to the Edward Weissman papers, 1971-2008.
Weissman, Edward papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Edward Weissman papers, 1971-2008.
13-1-3848
Weissman
3 cubic feet.
Correspondence, printed material, publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Subject files relating to all aspects of library administration.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Assistant to the Cornell University Librarian, Cornell University Library.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Subject files relating to all aspects of library administration. Includes files about implementing early library management and catalog systems, including NOTIS, BLIS (Biblio-Techniques Library Information System), and RLIN.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Weissman, Edward.; Cornell University. Libraries.
Titles:
NOTIS (Computer system); BLIS (Computer system)
Subjects:
Library administrators -- New York (State) -- Ithaca.; Libraries -- Automation.; Academic libraries -- New York (State) -- Ithaca -- Administration.; Library administration.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Recon (Record Conversion) Project, 1980-1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Recon Project, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Recon Project, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Recon Project-Costs, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- "S" Transfer Project, 1971-1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- "QE" Transfer-from Olin to Engineering, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- SCRLC Proposal, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Conversion of PR Records, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Regional Automation Grant from SCRLC, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Luce Foundation Recon Project, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Luce Foundation Recom Project, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Great Collections Presrvation Projcet, 1987-1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Latin American Recon Project, 1988-1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Latin American Recon Project, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Johnson Graduate School Recon Project, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Uris Library Recon Project, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Fine Arts Recon Project, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Music Recon Project, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Music Recon Project, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Music Recon Project, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Xerox Digitization Project, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- NYS Digitization Project, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- ILR, Geneva, Law, Hillmann Recon Projects, 1984-1995 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Orientation Program for New Librarians, 1983-1989 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- RLG/OCLC Assessments, 1978-1986 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Central Technical Services, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Task Force on the Future of the Card Catalog, 1976-1980 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Sub-Committee on Closing the Card Catalog, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- King Research Card Catalog Study, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Task Force - Bibliographic Control, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Task Force - Bibliographic Control, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Task Force - Bibliographic Control, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Task Force - Selecting a Library Management System, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Working Group on the BLIS Implementation, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Working Group on the BLIS Implementation, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Working Group on the BLIS Implementation - Tables, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Site Visits to Look at Potential Library Management Systems, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Proposal to Transfer Processing from RLIN to Notis, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- NOTIS File Conversion Specifications Group, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- NOTIS File Conversion Specifications Group, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- NOTIS Records, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- NOTIS Records, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Policy and Planning Board, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Policy and Planning Board, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Senior Management Group, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Senior Management Group, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Senior Management Group, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Senior Management Group, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Senior Management Group (SMG), 1997 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- University Library Management Team (ULMT), 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- University Library Management Team, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Library Executive Team, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Library Management Team, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Library Management Team, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Library Management Team, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Library Management Team, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Library Management Team, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Library Management Team, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Library Management Team, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Library Management Team, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Library Management Team, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Library Management Team, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Library Management Team, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Library Management Team, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Library Management Team, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Library Management Team, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Library Management Team, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Library Management Team, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Library Management Team, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Library Management Team, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Library Management Team, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Library Management Team, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- CUL Administration Team, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- CUL Administration Team, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 19)